

Sanusi Rasheed

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Motivated, teamwork-oriented frontend developer with significant experience in developing high-impact websites. Aiming to flourish as a front-end developer by combining a diverse background with excellent technical skills. Interested in adding value to a dynamic organization that recognizes and encourages efficiency and accountability.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Location

Lagos, Nigeria

CONTACT

- sanrosheed01@gmail.com
- +234 8124174008
- https://my-portfolio-tailwind-red.vercel.app
- in Sanusi Rasheed
- Sanrosheed

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer Intern

TIIDELAB April 2023-Dec 2023

- Wrote code in various languages, including HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, and React.
- Collaborated with a team and actively participated in a variety of projects, helping to design the front end of websites.
- Built real-world projects which include an attendance tracking website that helps organizations and schools to monitor the performance of their workers and students
- Worked with a team to develop an electronic health record system designed to store patients' medical records and manage appointments. Participated in the development of the website's user interface (UI) and the integration of its functionalities.

Data Analyst

SAN HOSPITAL AND MATERNITY HOME

Sep 2017- Present

- Optimized data collection procedures and generated reports on weekly and monthly basis.
- Performed detailed analysis, including income statements, balance sheets, and cash flow statements, to evaluate company performance and identify areas for improvement.
- Conducted ad-hoc analysis and special projects as assigned, demonstrating strong problem-solving and analytical skills.

EDUCATION

B.Sc Biochemistry

LAGOS STATE UNIVERSITY, OJO, LAGOS

Jan 2019- May 2023

HARD SKILLS

HTML5	CSS	Tailwind	Git	JavaScript	React	Responsive web design
-------	-----	----------	-----	------------	-------	-----------------------

SOFT SKILLS

Effective communicat	ion Teamwork	Problem solving	Leadership	
Time management	Presentation skills	Networking	Critical thinking	Analytical skills